<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Campus on The California Tech</title>
    <link>/categories/campus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Campus on The California Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/campus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Growing Student Body Leads to Undergraduate Housing Shortage</title>
      <link>/2023/03/housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/housing/</guid>
      <description>For almost as long as Caltech had undergraduate students, the institute has guaranteed its students housing on campus for four years. This policy stood until 2021, when the Institute had a record yield rate of 54% of admitted students. This, combined with the numerous students who took a gap year during the 2020-21 school year, meant that there were too many students for the nine residences; “there [were] approximately 870 beds available with approximately 970 undergraduate students,” as stated in the Assistant Director of Undergraduate Housing, Joe Benethaum’s initial email to the undergraduate students relaying the housing changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Hima Vatti About the Caltech Title IX Program</title>
      <link>/2023/03/title-ix-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/title-ix-interview/</guid>
      <description>How long have you worked in the Equity and Title IX office?
I became Caltech’s Title IX Coordinator and started managing the Equity and Title IX Office in July 2019. We address issues of sexual misconduct, relationship violence, and stalking, as well as unlawful discrimination and harassment based on legally protected characteristics, including sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, race, national origin, ethnicity, medical conditions, disabilities, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
