<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vol. CXXVI, Issue 1 on The California Tech</title>
    <link>/tags/vol.-cxxvi-issue-1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vol. CXXVI, Issue 1 on The California Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/vol.-cxxvi-issue-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fizz: Coming to a Campus Near You</title>
      <link>/2023/03/fizz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/fizz/</guid>
      <description>On the first day of winter term, on-campus students woke up to find small glossy flyers outside their doors, advertising an app called “Fizz”. Throughout the day, representatives gave out free donuts outside Hameetman to incentivize students to download the app. The invasion had begun.
Fizz is a social media platform designed specifically for college students: you need a university email to create an account, and you can only interact with your university’s feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing Student Body Leads to Undergraduate Housing Shortage</title>
      <link>/2023/03/housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/housing/</guid>
      <description>For almost as long as Caltech had undergraduate students, the institute has guaranteed its students housing on campus for four years. This policy stood until 2021, when the Institute had a record yield rate of 54% of admitted students. This, combined with the numerous students who took a gap year during the 2020-21 school year, meant that there were too many students for the nine residences; “there [were] approximately 870 beds available with approximately 970 undergraduate students,” as stated in the Assistant Director of Undergraduate Housing, Joe Benethaum’s initial email to the undergraduate students relaying the housing changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Haven&#39;t Been Paid for My Work in Three Years. What&#39;s Up With That?</title>
      <link>/2023/03/kenny-pay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/kenny-pay/</guid>
      <description>It was a simpler time three years ago. On March 3rd, 2020, students submitted their assignments they wrote up on sheets of paper to physical drop boxes, the most interesting thing that happened on campus in the past two weeks was a party put on by the undergrad house we now know as Venerable, and the article with title &amp;ldquo;Coronavirus Cases Pop Up Across U.S. Over Weekend&amp;rdquo; wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big enough deal to be the first thing you see as you picked up the day&amp;rsquo;s issue of The California Tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Hima Vatti About the Caltech Title IX Program</title>
      <link>/2023/03/title-ix-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/title-ix-interview/</guid>
      <description>How long have you worked in the Equity and Title IX office?
I became Caltech’s Title IX Coordinator and started managing the Equity and Title IX Office in July 2019. We address issues of sexual misconduct, relationship violence, and stalking, as well as unlawful discrimination and harassment based on legally protected characteristics, including sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, race, national origin, ethnicity, medical conditions, disabilities, and religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinstate, It Cannot Wait: A collective call to action for an international scholar</title>
      <link>/2023/03/reinstate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/reinstate/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, on the 24th of February, a group of about 40 Caltech graduate students and postdoctoral researchers delivered a petition signed by over 400 of our colleagues, in support of an international graduate student. Facing unjust retaliatory action from the Institute, the student risks losing their graduate student status at Caltech permanently, and with it, their legal immigration status in the US. Fully unfurled, the petition stretched seven feet long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CRC is Back</title>
      <link>/2023/03/the-crc-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/the-crc-is-back/</guid>
      <description>One of the best things about Caltech is the autonomy that students are afforded. It’s no exaggeration to say life as we know it would not be possible without the Honor Code. We often take this implicit trust between students, faculty, and staff, for granted. But as in any relationship, this trust can start to degrade over time if it is not reassessed and reaffirmed.
By many accounts, the past few years have been a rough patch &amp;ndash; owing in large part to the pandemic, among several other factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Mannion&#39;s Recipes</title>
      <link>/2023/03/mannion-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2023/03/mannion-recipes/</guid>
      <description>Smoked Salmon Tartare
Ingredients
One side of smoked salmon 1 ½ cups finely chopped shallots 1 cup finely chopped chives EVO to moisten Salt to taste (tbsp?) Creme fraiche and chive tips to garnish Chop up salmon, add chives and shallots, moisten with EVO. Sprinkle and stir salt to taste. Place some on crostini/cracker/etc. Squirt dollop of creme fraiche. Garnish with chive tips. Goat cheese mousse and parmesan cups
Ingredients</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
